Sculpture Lantern Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Germany (Box 44)
  - Reinassance (Box 47)
    - 18th – 20th Centuries (Box 47)
      - Uhlmann, Hans, 1900- (Box 51)
      - Vischer, Hans (Box 51)
      - Vischer, Peter, the Elder, 1460-1529 & Vischer, Peter the Younger (Box 51)
      - Vischer, Peter, Workshop of (Box 51)
      - Vostell, Wolf, 1932- (Box 51)
      - Witten, Han, ac.1500-1525 (Box 51)
      - Woyers, Kersten (Box 52)
- Holland (Box 52)
  - Various Artists (Box 52)
  - Doesburg, Theo van, 1883-1931 (Box 52)
  - Gerhard, Hubert, 1540/50-1931 (Box 52)
  - Vantongerloo, Georges, 1886- (Box 52)
  - Vordemberg, Gildewart (Box 52)
  - Vries, Adriaen de, 1560-1626 (Box 52)
- Hungary (Box 52)
  - Moholy-Nagy, Laszlo, 1895-1946 (Box 52)
- Italy (Box 52)
  - Romanesque (Box 52)
    - Various (Box 52)
    - Animals (Box 52)
    - Capitals (Box 52)
    - Crucifixes (Box 52)
    - Figures (Box 52)
    - Fonts (Box 52)
    - Pulpits (Box 52)
    - Reliefs (Box 52)
    - Bronze Door (Box 52)
    - Benevento (Box 52)
      - Cathedral (Box 52–53)
    - Monreale (Box 53)
      - Cathedral doors (Box 53)
    - Pisa (Box 53)
      Xx for cathedral doors, sculpture Italy, Bonannus of Pisa Trani
      - Cathedral doors (Box 53)
    - Verona (Box 53)
      - S. Zeno doors (Box 53)
  - Gothic (Box 53)
    - Various (Box 53)
    - 13th century (Box 53)
      - Animals (Box 53)
      - Figures (Box 53)
      - Various titles (Box 53)
      - S. Peter, bronze in S. Peter's (Box 53)
      - Heads (Box 53)
      - Reliefs (Box 53)
      - Tombs (Box 53)
    - 14th century (Box 53)
      - Various titles (Box 53)
      - Porto Della Mandorla (Box 53)
        - Various (Box 53–54)
        - Attributed to Giovanni (Box 54)
        - Attributed to Nicolo Lamberti (Box 54)
        - Attributed to Lorenzo Di Giovanni D'Ambrogio (Box 54)
      - Tombs (Box 54)
        - Various (Box 54)
  - Renaissance (Box 54)
    - Various titles (Box 54)
    - Altar (Box 54)
    - Mask (Box 54)
    - 15th century (Box 54)
      - Various Titles (Box 54)
      - Arco D'Alfonso D'Aragona (Box 54–55)
      - Figures (Box 55)
        - Various (Box 55)
        - Man of Sorrows (Box 55)
      - Forgeries (Box 55)
      - Monuments (Box 55)
      - Portrait Busto (Box 55)
      - Reliefs (Box 55)
      - Reliefs (Box 55)
      - Tombs (Box 55)
      - Virgin & Child (Group, reliefs) (Box 55–56)
    - 16th century (Box 56)
  - Baroque (Box 56)
    - 17th century (Box 56)
    - Various titles (Box 56)
    - Varallo Sacro Monte (Box 56)
    - Varese (Box 56)
  - 18th Century (Box 56)
  - Modern (Box 56)
    - 19th Centurry (Box 56)
    - 20th century (Box 56)
      - Various Artists (Box 56)
      - Agostino di Duccio, 1418-1498 (Box 56)
        - Florence (Box 56)
        - Perugia (Box 56)
        - Rimini (Box 56)
          - Various (Box 56)
          - School of Duccio (Box 57)
      - Alberti, Leon B., 1404-1472 (Box 57)
      - Algardi, Alessandro, 1598-1654 (Box 57)
        - Various (Box 57)
        - Rome (Box 57)
      - Amadeo, Giovanni A., 1477-1522 (Box 57)
      - Ammanati, Bartolomeo, 1511-1592 (Box 57)
      - Andreotti, Libero (Box 57)
      - Andriolo de Santi (Box 57)
      - Antelami, Benedetto, ca.1150-1230 (Box 57)
      - L'Antico (P.J.A. Bonacolsi), 1460-1528 (Box 57)
      - Antonio Federighi, 1420-1490 (Box 57)
      - Aprile, Francesco (Box 57)
      - Arnoldi, Alberto, ca.1351-1364 (Box 58)
      - Arnolfo di Cambio, 1260-1302 (Box 58)
      - Aspetti, Tiziano, 1565-1607 (Box 58)
      - Banco, Nanni di, ca. 1383-1471 (Box 58)
        - Florence (Box 58)
          - Cathedral (Duomo) (Box 58)
            - Assumption of the Virgin on Porta Della Mandorla (Box 58)
            - Assumption of the Virgin: Angels (Box 58)
            - Assumption of the Virgin: Virgin (Box 58)
            - Prophet Isaiah (Box 58)
            - Prophet from Porta Della Mandorla (Box 58)
          - Cathedral Museum (Box 58)
            - Angel of the Annunciation (Box 58)
            - S. Luke (Box 58)
          - OrsanMichele (Box 58)
            - Four Crowned Saints (Box 58)
            - S. Eligias (Box 59)
            - S. Philip (Box 59)
      - Bandinelli, Baccio, 1488-1560 (Box 59)
      - Baroncelli, Nicolo & Giovanni, ca.1434-1453 (Box 59)
      - Bastianini, Giovanni, 1830-1868 (Box 59)
      - Begarelli, A., 1497-1539 (Box 59)
      - Bellano, Bartolomeo, 1434-1497 (Box 59)
      - Benedetto da Maiano, 1442-1497 (Box 59)
        - Various (Box 59)
        - Florence (Box 59)
        - Naples (Box 59)
      - Bernini, Giovanni Lorenzo, 1598-1680 (Box 59)
        - Florence (Box 59)
        - London (Box 59)
        - Rome (Box 60)
          - Various Titles (Box 60)
          - Borghese Gallery (Box 60)
            - Various (Box 60)
            - Apollo & Daphne (Box 60)
            - Cardinal Scipione Borghese (Box 60)
            - David (Box 60)
            - Rape of Proserpine (Box 60)
          - S. Andrea Delle Fratte (Box 60)
          - S. Francisco a Ripa (Box 60)
          - S. Lorenzo in Lucina (Box 60)
          - S. Maria della Vittoria (Box 60)
            - S. Teresa Cornaro Chapel (Box 60)
          - S. Maria Del Popolo (Box 60)
          - S. Peter's (Box 60)
            - Various Titles (Box 60)
            - Altar & Chair of S. Peter (Box 60)
            - Tomb of Urban VIII (Box 60)
          - Piazza Barbarini (Box 60)
          - Piazza Navona (Box 60)
            - Fountain of Four Rivers (Box 60)
          - Vatican (Box 60)
            - Various Titles (Box 60)
            - Constanitne the Creat (Box 60)
        - Siena (Box 61)
        - Versailles (Box 61)
        - Washington (Box 61)
      - Bertoldo Di Giovanni, 1410-1491 (Box 61)
      - Boccioni, Umberto, 1882-1916 (Box 61)
      - Bonannus of Pisa, ca.1174-1196 (Box 61)
      - Bonino da Campione, ca.1349-1397 (Box 61)
      - Bregno, Andrea, 1418-1508 (Box 61)
      - Briosco, Andrea, 1470-1532 (Box 61)
      - Brunelleschi, Filippo, 1377-1446 (Box 61)
        - Various (Box 61)
        - Florence (Box 61)
          - Various (Box 61)
          - Borgello (Box 61)
          - S. Maria Novello (Box 61)
        - Pistoia (Box 61)
      - Buon, Bartolommeo (Box 61)
      - Buon, Giovanni (Box 61)
      - Buggiano (Andrea Cavalcanti) (Box 61)
      - Buglioni (Box 62)
      - Bussola, Dionigi, ac.1645-1687 (Box 62)
      - Canova, Antonio, 1757-1822 (Box 62)
        - Various (Box 62)
        - Rome (Box 62)
          - Various (Box 62)
          - Vatican Museum (Box 62)
          - S. Peter's (Box 62)
          - Villa Borghese (Box 62)
        - Venice (Box 62)
        - Washington (Box 62)
      - Canova, Antonio, 1757-1822 (Box 62)
        - Various titles (Box 62)
        - Rome (Box 62)
      - Caroni, E. (Box 62)
      - Cattaneo, Danese, 1508-1573 (Box 62)
      - Cavallini, Francesco (Box 62)
      - Cellini, Benvenuto, 1500-1571 (Box 62)
        - Florence (Box 62)
          - Bargello (Box 62)
          - Logia Dei Lanzi (Box 62)
        - Vienna (Box 62)
      - Ceracchi, Giusepe, 1751-1801 (Box 62)
      - Cioli, Valerio, 1529-1579 (Box 62)
      - Ciuffagni, Bernardo (attributed) (Box 62)
      - Civitali, Matteo, 1436-1501 (Box 63)
        - Various (Box 63)
        - Lucca (Box 63)
      - Cosma, Giovanni (Box 63)
      - Cozzarelli, Guidocc (Box 63)
      - Dalmata, Giovanni, 1440-1576 (Box 63)
      - Danti, Vincenzo, 1530-1576 (Box 63)
      - Delli, Dello, ac.1424-1471 (Box 63)
      - Depero, Fortunato, 1892-1960 (Box 63)
      - De Sanctis, A. School of (Box 63)
      - Desiderio da Settignano, 1428-1464 (Box 63)
        - Various Titles (Box 63)
        - Berlin (Box 63)
        - Florence (Box 63)
          - Bargello (Box 63)
          - S. Croce (Box 63)
          - Marsuppini Tomb (Box 63)
            - Details (Box 63)
          - S. Lorenzo (Box 64)
            - Tabernacle (Box 64)
              - Various (Box 64)
              - Details (Box 64)
        - London (Box 64)
        - New York (Box 64)
        - Paris (Box 64)
        - Turin (Box 64)
        - Vienna (Box 65)
        - Washington (Box 65)
          - National Gallery (Box 65)
            - Various Titles (Box 65)
            - Young St. John the Baptist (Box 65)
            - S. Jerome in the Dessert (Box 65)
            - Marietta Strozzi (Box 65)
            - Isotta da Rimini (Box 65)
      - Domenico Di Niccolo (Box 65)
      - Donatello, ca.1386-1466 (Box 65)
        - Various titles (Box 65)
        - Berlin (Box 65)
        - Florence (Box 65)
          - Baptistry (Box 65)
            - Mary Magdalena (Box 65)
          - Bargello (Box 65)
            - Various (Box 65)
            - Atys (Amor) (Box 65)
            - Crucifixion (Box 65)
            - David (bronze) (Box 65)
            - David (marble) (Box 65)
            - S. Geroge (Box 66)
            - S. John the Baptist (Box 66)
              - Campanille (Box 66)
          - Opera del Duomo (Box 66)
            - Abraham & Isaac (Box 66)
            - Cantoria (Box 66)
            - Prophets (Box 66)
            - Habakkuk (Box 66)
            - Jeremiah (Box 66)
            - Moses (Box 66)
            - S. John Evangelist (Box 66)
          - OrSanmichele (Box 67)
            - Various titles (Box 67)
            - S. Mark (Box 67)
          - Pal. Vecchio (Box 67)
            - Judith and Holofernes (Box 67)
          - S. Croce (Box 67)
            - Annunciation (Box 67)
            - Crucifix (Box 67)
            - S. Louis of Toulouse (Box 67)
          - S. Lorenzo (Box 67)
            - North Pulpit (Box 67)
            - South Pulpit (Box 68)
          - S. Lorenzo, Old Sacristy (Box 68)
            - Various (Box 68)
            - Apostle doors (Box 68)
            - Martyr door (Box 68)
        - London (Box 68)
          - Various (Box 68)
          - Brancacci Relief (Box 68)
        - Naples (Box 68)
        - Padua (Box 69)
          - Gattamelata (Box 69)
          - S. Antonio (Box 69)
            - High Altar S. Antonio (Box 69)
              - Reconstructions (Box 69)
              - Figures of Saints (Box 69)
              - Virgin and Child (Box 69)
              - Ass of Rimini (Box 69)
              - Heart of the Miser (Box 69)
              - Healing Irascible Son (Box 69)
              - Miracle Speaking Babe (Box 69)
              - Symbols of the Evangelists (Box 69)
              - Angels Panels (Box 70)
            - Crucifix (Box 70)
        - Paris (Box 70)
        - Prato (Box 70)
        - Rome (Box 70)
        - Siena (Box 70)
          - Baptistery (Box 70)
            - Baptismal Font (Box 70)
              - Angels (Box 70)
              - Faith (Box 70)
              - Hope (Box 70)
            - Feat of Herod (Box 70)
          - Cathedral (Box 70)
            - Pecci Tomb (Box 70)
            - Madonna del Perdoro (Box 70)
            - S. John Baptist (Box 70)
        - Torrita (Box 70)
        - Venice (Box 70)
        - Washington (Box 70)
      - Dossena, Alceo (Box 71)
      - Dupre, Giovanni, 1817-1882 (Box 71)
      - Faggi, Alfred (Box 71)
      - Ferrata, Ercole, 1610-1686 (Box 71)
      - Ferrucci, Andrea di Piero, 1465-1526 (Box 71)
      - Ferruci, Francesco, 1438-1493 (Box 71)
      - Filarete, Antonio, 1400-1469 (Box 71)
      - Finelli, Giuliano, 1601-1657 (Box 71)
      - Foggini, Giovanni B., 1652-1725 (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - Washington (Box 71)
      - Fontana, Annibale, 1540-1587 (Box 71)
      - Francesco di Giorgio, 1439-1502 (Box 71)
        - Various (Box 71)
        - Fogliano (Box 72)
        - London (Box 72)
        - Siena (Box 72)
        - Washington (Box 72)
      - Gagini, Antonello, 1478-1536 (Box 72)
      - Gagini, Domenico, 1448-1536 (Box 72)
      - Gano Da Siena (Box 72)
      - Ghiberti, Lorenzo, 1378-1455 (Box 72)
        - Florence (Box 72)
          - Baptistery (Box 72)
            - North doors (Box 72)
              - Diagrams (Box 72)
              - Whole door (Box 72)
              - Details (Box 72)
            - South doors (Box 73)
            - East doors (Box 73)
              - Diagrams (Box 73)
              - Whole door (Box 73)
                - Creation & Expulsion (Box 73)
                - Cain & Abel (Box 73)
                - Jacob & Esau (Box 73)
                - Joseph (Box 73)
                - Joshua (Box 73)
                - Noah (Box 73)
                - Sacrifice of Isaac (Box 73)
                - Moses (Box 73)
                - Solomon & Sheba (Box 73)
                - David & Goliath (Box 73)
                - Border Relief & Prophet (Box 73)
          - Bargello (Box 73)
          - OrSanmichele (Box 73)
          - S. Maria Nuova (Box 74)
            - Various (Box 74)
            - Siena (Box 74)
      - Giorgetti, Antonio, d.1670 (Box 74)
      - Giovanni d'Ambrogio (Box 74)
      - Giovanni di Balducci, 1290-1350 (Box 74)
      - Giovanni da Bologna, 1524-1608 (Box 74)
        - Bologna (Box 74)
        - Florence (Box 74)
          - Various (Box 74)
          - Mercury (Box 74)
          - Rape of the Sabines (Box 74)
        - New York (Box 74)
      - Giovanni da Firenze, ca.1343-1345 (Box 74)
      - Giovanni & Pacio Da Firence (Box 74)
      - Giovanni D'Enrico (Box 74)
      - Giovanni Da Palermo, Fra (Box 74)
      - Giovanni Di Stefano (Box 74)
      - Guarnerio, P (Box 74)
      - Guglielmo Da Pisa (Box 74)
      - Guido Da Como (Box 74)
      - Isaia Da Pisa (Box 74)
      - Jacopino da Tradate (Box 74)
      - Lamberti, Niccolo (Box 75)
      - Lamberti, Pietro (Box 75)
      - Landi, Neroccio (Box 75)
        - Various (Box 75)
        - Siena (Box 75)
      - Lardera, Berto, 1911- (Box 75)
      - Laurana, Francesco, 1420-1502 (Box 75)
        - Florence (Box 75)
        - New York (Box 75)
        - Palermo (Box 75)
        - Paris (Box 76)
        - Washington (Box 76)
      - Leonardo da Vinci, 1452-1519 (Box 76)
      - Leoni, Leone, 1509-1590 (Box 76)
      - Leopardi, Alessandro (Box 76)
      - Lombardi, Alfonzo (Box 76)
      - Lombardo, Antonio, ca.1458-1516 (Box 76)
      - Lombardo, Pietro, ca.1435-1515 (Box 76)
      - Lombardo, Tullio, ca.1455-1532 (Box 76)
      - Lorenzo Di Giovanni D'Ambrogio (Box 76)
      - Lorenzi, Stoldo, 1534-1583 (Box 76)
      - Maderna, Stefano, 1576-1636 (Box 76)
      - Magnelli, Alberto (Box 76)
      - Maiano, Benedetto (Box 77)
      - Maitani, Lorenzo, 1275-1330 (Box 77)
      - Manzu, Giacomo, 1908- (Box 77)
      - Marchiori, Giovanni (Box 77)
      - Martini, Arturo, 1889-1947 (Box 77)
      - Mascherini, Marcello, 1906- (Box 77)
      - Mascoli Master (Box 77)
      - Masegne, Jacobello & Pier, 1383-1409 (Box 77)
        - Bologna (Box 77)
          - Various (Box 77)
          - S. Francesco (Box 77)
            - High Altar (Box 77)
          - Annunciation (Box 78)
          - Crucifixion (Box 78)
          - Angels musicians (Box 78)
      - Maso di Bartolommeo, 1406-1456 (Box 78)
      - Mazzoni, Guido, 1450-1518 (Box 78)
      - Mercia, Niccolo di Cecco del, -1370 (Box 78)
      - Michelangelo, 1475-1564 (Box 78)
        - Berlin (Box 78)
        - Bologna (Box 78)
        - Bruges (Box 78)
        - Florence (Box 78)
          - Accademia (Box 78)
            - Various (Box 78)
            - Captives (Box 78)
            - David (Box 79)
              - Various (Box 79)
              - As it would have appeared in the Loggia Dei Lenze (Box 79)
              - Copy in piazza Signoria (Box 79)
              - Details (Box 79)
                - Hand (Box 79)
                - Head (Box 79)
                - Torso (Box 79)
            - S. Matthew (Box 79)
            - Pieta Palestrina (Box 79)
          - Bargello (Box 79)
            - Bacchus (Box 79)
            - Brutus (Box 79)
            - David (Box 79)
            - Madonna & Child with S. John (Box 79)
          - Cathedral (Box 80)
          - Casa Buonarroti (Box 80)
            - Various (Box 80)
            - Crucifix (Box 80)
            - Battle of Centaurs (Box 80)
            - Madonna of the Stairs (Box 80)
            - Sketches for David (Box 80)
          - S. Lorenzo Medici Chapel (Box 80)
            - Various (Box 80)
            - Madonna & Child (Box 80)
            - Tomb of Lorenzo (Box 80)
              - Lorenzo (Box 80)
              - Dawn (Box 80)
              - Twilight (Box 80)
            - Tomb of Giuliano (Box 80)
              - Various (Box 80)
              - Giuliano (Box 81)
              - Day (Box 81)
              - Night (Box 81)
          - Pal. Vecchio (Box 81)
        - Leningrad (Box 81)
        - London (Box 81)
        - Milan (Box 81)
        - Paris (Box 81)
          - Louvre (Box 81)
            - "Dying" Slave Figure (Box 81)
            - "Rebel" slave figure (Box 81)
        - Rome (Box 81)
          - S. Maria Della Minerva (Box 81)
          - S. Peter's (Box 81)
            - Pieta (Box 81)
          - S. Pietro in Vincoli (Box 82)
            - Tomb of Jilius II (Box 82)
          - Siena (Box 82)
      - Michelozzo, (attributed to) 1396-1472 (Box 82)
        - Various (Box 82)
        - Florence (Box 82)
        - Montepulciano (Box 82)
        - Naples (Box 82)
        - Prato (Box 82)
      - Mino da Fiesole, 1430-1484 (Box 82)
        - Various (Box 82)
        - Berlin (Box 82)
        - Fiesole (Box 82)
        - Florence (Box 83)
        - Paris (Box 83)
        - Rome (Box 83)
        - Washington (Box 83)
      - Mochi, Francesco, 1580-1654 (Box 83)
      - Modigliani, Amadeo, 1884-1920 (Box 83)
      - Montelupo, Raffaello da, 1505-1566/7 (Box 83)
      - Monti, R. (Box 83)
      - Monrlaiter, Giovanni Maria (Box 83)
      - Nanni di Bartolo, 1419-1451 (Box 83)
      - Negri, Mario, 1916- (Box 83)
      - Niccolo dell'Arca, 1463-1494 (Box 83)
        - Bologna (Box 83)
          - Palace Communale (Box 83)
          - S. Domenico (Box 83)
          - S. Maria Della Vita (Box 84)
      - Niccolo de D'Arezzo (Box 84)
      - Onofri, Vincenzo, 1503-1524 (Box 84)
      - Orcagna, Andrea di Cione, 1308-1368 (Box 84)
      - Paerino, D. (Box 84)
      - Paladini, Filippo (Box 84)
      - Persico, Luigi,1791-1860 (Box 84)
      - Piccolomini Master (Box 84)
      - Pierino da Vinci, 1520-1554 (Box 84)
      - Pisano, Andrea, 1270-1349 (Box 84)
        - Florence (Box 84)
          - Baptistry (Box 84)
            - South Doors (Box 84)
          - Campanile (Box 84)
            - Agriculture (Box 84)
            - Cart Driver (Box 85)
            - Daedalus (Box 85)
            - Fishing (Box 85)
            - Hercules & Cacus (Box 85)
            - Painter (Box 85)
            - Sculptor (Box 85)
            - The Weaver (Box 85)
            - Tubulcain Metal worker (Box 85)
            - Jubal Musician (Box 85)
            - Jabal Shepherd (Box 85)
            - First work of men (Box 85)
            - Creation of Adam & Eve (Box 85)
            - Medical Art (Box 85)
      - Pisano, Giovanni, 1245-1314 (Box 85)
        - Pisa (Box 85)
        - Pistoia (Box 85)
        - Siena (Box 86)
      - Pisano, Niccolo (Box 86)
        - Bologna (Box 86)
        - Pisa (Box 86)
        - Siena (Box 86)
      - Pisano, Niccolo & Giovanni (Box 86)
        - Perugia (Box 86)
          - Fountain (Box 86)
      - Pisano, Nino, ca.1349-1368 (Box 86)
      - Pollaiuolo, Antonio, 1432-1498 (Box 86)
        - Florence (Box 86)
          - Various (Box 87)
          - Bargello (Box 87)
        - Rome (Box 87)
          - S. Peter's (Box 87)
      - Porta, Guglielmo della, ca.1531-1557 (Box 87)
      - Queirolo, Francesco, 1704-1762 (Box 87)
      - Quercia, Jacopo della, 1367-1438 (Box 87)
        - Bologna (Box 87)
          - Various (Box 87)
          - S. Petronio (Box 87)
            - Old Testament (Box 87)
              - Sacrifice of Cain & Abel (Box 87)
              - Noah's Ark (Box 87)
              - Creation of Adam & Eve (Box 87)
              - Temptation (Box 88)
              - Expulsion (Box 88)
              - Condemnation of work (Box 88)
            - New Testament (Box 88)
              - Nativity (Box 88)
              - Adoration of the Magi (Box 88)
              - Madonna & Child (Box 88)
              - Flight into Egypt (Box 88)
              - Presentation in the Temple (Box 88)
        - Ferrara (Box 88)
        - Florence (Box 88)
        - London (Box 88)
        - Lucca (Box 88)
          - Duomo (Box 88)
            - Various (Box 88)
            - Tomb of Ilaria del Carreto (Box 88)
        - Siena (Box 89)
          - Various (Box 89)
          - Baptistry (Box 89)
          - Palace Communale (Palace Publico) (Box 89)
            - Fonte Gaia (Box 89)
        - Washington (Box 90)
      - Raggi, Antonio, 1624-1686 (Box 90)
      - Raphael Sanzio, 1483-1520 (Box 90)
      - Raverti, Matteo (style of) (Box 90)
      - Ricci, Giovanni, 1440-1523 (Box 90)
      - Ricciarelli, Daniele, 1509-1566 (Box 90)
      - Il Riccio (Box 90)
        Xx Briosco, Andrea
      - Rivalta, A. (Box 90)
      - Rizzo, Antonio, ca.1465-1499 (Box 90)
      - Robbia, Andrea della, 1435-1525 (Box 90)
        - Various (Box 90)
        - Florence (Box 91)
          - Bargello (Box 91)
          - Ospedale Degli Innocenci (Box 91)
        - La Verne (Box 91)
        - London (Box 91)
        - New York (Box 91)
        - Pistoia (Box 91)
      - Robbia, Giovanni della, 1469-1529 (Box 91)
        X Della Robbia, Giovanni
        - Florence (Box 91)
        - Pistoia (Box 91)
      - Robbia, Girolamo della, 1488-1566 (Box 91)
      - Robbia, Luca della, 1400-1482 (Box 91)
        - Cleveland (Box 91)
        - Florence (Box 91)
          - Various (Box 91)
          - Bargello (Box 92)
            - Virgin & Child (Box 92)
          - Campanille (Box 92)
          - Cathedral (Box 92)
          - Cathedral Museum (Duomo) (Box 92)
            - Cantoria (Box 92)
              - Various (Box 92)
              - Allehujah (side panels) (Box 92)
              - Laudate Eum In (Box 92)
            - S. Croce (Box 92–93)
            - S. Trinita (Box 93)
        - London (Box 93)
        - Paris (Box 93)
          - Various (Box 93)
          - School of Della Robbia (Box 93)
      - Romano, Giovanni Christoforo, ca.1470-1512 (Box 93)
      - Rosselli, Domenico di G., ca. 1439-1497 (Box 93)
      - Rossellino, Antonio, 1427-1479 (Box 93)
        - Various (Box 93)
        - Empoli (Box 93)
        - Florence (Box 93)
          - Various (Box 93)
          - Bargello (Box 93)
          - S. Croce (Box 93)
          - S. Miniato (Box 93)
        - London (Box 93)
        - Naples (Box 93–94)
        - New York (Box 94)
      - Rossellino, Bernardo, 1407-1464 (Box 94)
        - Arezzo (Box 94)
        - Empoli (Box 94)
        - Florence (Box 94)
          - S. Croce (Box 94)
      - Rosso, IL (Box 94)
      - Rosso, Medardo, 1858-1928 (Box 94)
      - Rustici, G.F., 1474-1554 (Box 95)
      - San Gallo, Francesco da, 1494-1576 (Box 95)
      - Sangallo, Giuliano da, 1445-1516 (Box 95)
        X San Gallo, Giuliano da
      - Sanmartino, Giuseppe, 1720-1793 (Box 95)
      - Sansovino, Andrea, 1460-1529 (Box 95)
      - Sansovino, Jacopo, 1486-1570 (Box 95)
        - Various (Box 95)
        - Florence (Box 95)
      - Sant'Agata, Franceso da, ca.1520 (Box 95)
      - Santucci, Agostino (Box 96)
      - Serpotta, Giacomo (Box 96)
      - Severo da Ravenna, ca.1500 (Box 96)
      - Silvano, Gherardo, 1579-1675 (Box 96)
      - Simone Fiorentino (Box 96)
      - Slodtz, Michelangelo, 1705-1764 (Box 96)
      - Solari, Cristoforo, 1460-1527 (Box 96)
      - Solari, Giogio (Box 96)
      - Sulmona, Silvestro di Giovanni (Box 96)
      - Tacca, Pietro, 1577-1640 (Box 96)
      - Tenerani, Pietro, 1789-1869 (Box 96)
      - Tino di Camaino, 1285-1337 (Box 96)
      - Tombetta, E. (Box 96)
      - Torrigiano, Pietro, 1472-1528 (Box 96)
      - Turini, Giovanni, 1349-1438 (Box 96)